Guide to the Labor Union Constitutions, By-Laws and Agreements collection, 1883-1999 LAC0012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Labor Union Constitutions, By-Laws, Agreements and Other Records collection
1883-2009
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
LAC0012
19 Linear Feet
The collection is comprised of printed copies of various union constitutions and their by-laws, as well as contractual, wage and working condition agreements between unions and their employers, dating from 1883-1999. The majority of the unions represented are related to the railroad industry, including the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, the Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, and the United Transportation Union. Also included are constitutions and agreements of the United Steelworkers of America, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, and a variety of other labor organizations.
Arrangement
Organized into 2 series: Labor Union Constitutions and By-Laws and Agreements
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the constitutions, by-laws and agreements of local union branches in the United States and Canada. The material dates from 1883-2009.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Labor unions; Labor; Railroads; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Transportation
- Constitutions and By-Laws, 1883-1986; Series 1; 9 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This collection contains the constitutions and by-laws of local union branches in the United States and Canada. The material dates from 1883-1986.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Air Line Dispatchers Association, 5 October 1952; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1933-1955; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Operators, 1892-1953; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railways and Motor Coach Division 757, 1945; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1947-1953; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Amalgamated Meat Cutters And Butcher Workmen of America, 1944-1976; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Amalgamated Lithographers of America, 1948; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Brotherhood of Railway Police, 1945; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - American Communications Association, CIO, 1944; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - American Federation of Labor, 1954; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - American Flint Glass Workers' Union, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Flint Glass Workers of North America, 1952; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Newspaper Guild, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - American Postal Workers Union, August 1994; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - American Federation Of Express Workers, 17 September 1925; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - American Federation of History Workers, 1947-1953; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1945-1980; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - American Federation of Technical Engineers, 1952; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - American Federation Of Government Employees, 1946-1964; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - American Federation of Labor Railway Employes Department, 1938-1968; Series 1 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada, 1947-1952; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - American Federation of Railroad Workers, 1 Janaury 1924; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - American Federation Of States, County and Municipal Empl., 1946-1954; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - American Radio Association, 31 March - 4 April 1952; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - American Railway Supervisors Association Inc., 1893 - 1966; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - American Train Dispatchers Association, 1935-1964; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Associated Organizations of Shop Craft Employees of Great Northern Ry, 1931-1937; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Associated Unions of America Paper Workers Local 16, 1947; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Association of Boilermakers Helpers and Apprentices, 1 April 1930; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Association of Carmen, Helper and Apprentices, 1930-1938; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Association of Clerical Employees, A.T. and S.F. Ry, 1927-1932; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Association of Consolidated Metal Crafts, Helpers and Apprentices, 1938; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Association of Rock Island Mechanical and Power Plant, 1929; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Association of Shop Craft Employees of the SOuther Pacific Lines, 1929; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Association of Supervisors Southern Pacific Co, 1937; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Association of Licensed Officers Of The New Bedford Martha's Vineyard and Nantucket Steamboat Line, 1941; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Association of Locomotive Enginemen of Maryland, inc., 1937; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Association Of Maintenance of Equipment Employee of the Lehigh Valley Railroad, 1934; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Association of Maintenance of Equipment Employees of the Louisville and Nashville RR Mechanical Division, 1931-1939; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Association of Maintenance of Way and Miscellaneous Employees A.T. and S.F. Ry, 1934-1939; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Association of Mechanical Crafts, Helpers and Apprentices, D.E.R.G.W. Ry, 1922; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Association of Mechanical Department Employes of Fort Worth and Denver City Ry Co and Witchita Valley Ry Co., 1930; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Association of Mechanical Department Employes Toledo Peoria and Western RR, 1938; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Association of Power Plant Employees, 1928; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Association Of Railway Clerks and Associated Employees, 1938; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Association of Car Department Employees of the Atlanta, Birmingham and Coast RR Co., 1938; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Airline Riots Association International, 1944-1952; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Atlantic Coast Lines Signalmen's Association, 1926; Series 1 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Barbers and Beauty Culturists Union of America, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bakery and Confectionary Worker's International Union of America, 1951-1956; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Bangor and Aroostock Railroad Co. Mechanical Department Employes Association, Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Boot and Show Workers Union, 1948; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bricklayers, Masons, Plasterers' International Union of America, 1952; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, 1935-1967; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railway Carmen of America, 1935-1963; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood of Railway Linemen, 1934; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood of Railway Station Employes and Clerks, 1919; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen [Part 1 of 3], 1883-1954; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainment [Part 2 of 3], 1883-1964; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen [Part 3 of 3], 1883-1964; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Bay State Lodge no. 88, 1923; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 1 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 2 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 3 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 4 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 5 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 6 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [Part 7 of 7], 1922-1963; Series 1 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen of Great Northern Railway, 1934; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way employes Pennsylvania Federation, 1937; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1970; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1934-1974; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators, and Paperhangers of America, 1929-1947; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Brotherhood of Painters, Decorators and Paper Hangers of America, 1917-1986; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Shop Crafts of America Pennsylvania Railroad System, 1936; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Shop Crafts of America, 1935-1943; Series 1 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, 1936-1966; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Brotherhood's Relief and Compenation Fund, 1943-1946; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Brotherhood of Shoe and Allied Craftsmen, 1940; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 1936-1956; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Building Service Employees' International Union A.F. of L., 1947-1950; Series 1 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chauffeurs, Teamsters, Warehousemen, and Helpers, Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Colored Trainmen of America, 1929-1947; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Craft Of Machinist Ab. Delaware and Hudson Co., 1922; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Coopers' International Union of North America and A.F.L., 1947; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Communications Workers of America, 1947; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Commercial Telegraphers' Union, 1945-1951; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - CIO Local Industrial Unions, 1944; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Clerical Employes Association of the Oregon Short Line Railroad Association, 1925; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cigar Makers' International Union of America, 1944-1952; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Christian Labor Association of The United States, 1931-1955; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Conductors Trainmen and Yardmen, 1 December 1926; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Chicago Federation of Labor, 1933; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Association of Maintanence Of Equipment Department Employes, 1925; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dining Car Cooks, Waiters Of The Dining Car Employee Union, 1939; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Duluth, Missabec, and Iron Range Railway Co., 1934; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Dining car Employes Union Local 370, 1937; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Dining Car Employes, Local 354, 1942; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dining Car Employes Union, Local Union 351, Chicago, 1938; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Dining Car and Catering Local 582 Los Angeles, California, 1937; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Distillery, Rectifying and Wine Workers, 1946; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Denver and Salt Lake Clerks' and Affiliated Employees Unions, 1935-1938; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Express Drivers, Chauffeurs and Helpers Union, Local 909, 1936; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Erie System Clerical Association, 1923; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Engineers and Scientists of America, 1952; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Evangeline, Brotherhood od Railroad Trainmen, 1937; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Electrical Workers' Benefit Association, 1931-1947; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Federated Shop Crafts of The Bessemer and Lake Erie Railroad Company, 1939; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Federated Independant Texas Unions, 1941; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Federation of Telephone Workers of Pennsylvania, 1955; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Federation of Dyers, Finishers, Printers, and Bleachers, 1946; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Flight Engineers International Association, 1948; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Food, Tobacco, Agricultural and Aliied Workers Union, 1947; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Foreman's Assoication of America and Laws Governing Chapters, 1946-1951; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Frisco Association of Metal Crafts and Car Department Employee, 1923; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Fur Div. International Fur and Leather Workers Union USA and Canada, 1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Glass Bottle Blowers Association, 1946-1953; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Glaziers And Glass Workers, 1957; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Government And Civic Employees Organizing Committee, 1952; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Government Employes Council of the american Federation of Labor, 1945-1953; Series 1 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Grand International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1933-1956; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Grand International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1933-1956; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Grand International Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1933-1956; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Granite Cutter's International Association of America, 1941; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Gulf Coast Lines Employees' Hospital Association, 1951; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Harbor Boatmen's Union of Philadelphia Camden and Vicinity, 1930; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Employes International Alliance, 1934-1961; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Illinois Central Train Dispatchers' Association, 1937; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Independent Car Ferry Workers Union Of Great Lakes, 1941; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Independent Brotherhood Of Steam and Electrical Engineers, 1922; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Independent Pullman Workers Federation, 1935-1939; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Independent Shop Crafts Association of the Virginian Railway Co., 1934; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Industrial Union of Marine an Shipbuilding Workers of America, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Industrial Trades Union of America, Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Workers of the World, 1946; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Insurance Agents International Union, 1951; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employes and Moving Pictures Machine operators of the US and Canada, 1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1944-1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - International Association of Fire Fighters, 1945-1955; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Asbestos Workers, September 1952; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, 1946; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - International Association of Machinists [Part 1 of 2], 1933-1961; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - International Association of Machinists [Part 2 of 2], 1933-1961; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - International Association of Marble, Slate, and Stone Polishers, etc. of the United States and Canada, 1947; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - International Association of Railway Employees, 1942; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - International Brook and Whisk Makers' Union, 1945; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers [Part 1 of 3], 1927-1951; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers [Part 2 of 3], 1925; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers, and Helpers [Part 3 of 3], 1930-1961; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, June 29 to July 7, 1953; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - International Brotherhood of Bookbinders, 1941-1955; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1935-1952; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Wokers, 1954-1959; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood Of Firemen and Oilers, 1936-1961; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - International Brotherhood of Paper Makers, 1947-1949; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood Pulp, Sulphite and Paper Mill, 1944-1950; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Operative Potters, 1953; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers, December 1935; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers, 1940; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers, 1947; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters Chauffeurs, Stablemen and Helpers, 1952; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - International Clove Union Workers of America, 1946; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - International Federation of Technical Engineers, Architects and Draftsmens Unions, 1947; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of US and Canada, 1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - International Fur and Leather Workers Union of US an Canada, 1945; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - International Handbag, Luggage, Belt and Novelty Workers Union, 1951; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - International Hod Carriers' Building and Common Laborers' Union, 1946-1953; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - International Jewelry Workers' Union, 1944-1947; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - International Ladies Garment Workers' Union, 1944-1950; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - International Longshoremen's Association, 1935-1955; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - International Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, CIO, 1947-1955; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - International Mailers Union, 1947; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - International metal Engravers Union, 1942; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - International Molders and Foundry Workers Union, 1946-1947; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - International Molders and Foundry Workers, 1946-1951; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - International Order of Railway Yardmasters, N.D.; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots, 1947-1958; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - International Photo-Engravers Union, 1946-1955; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - International Plate Printers, Die Stampers and Engravers, 1938-1947; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistans, 1940-1948; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - International Printing Pressmen and Assistants Union of North America, 1952; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - International Stereotypers and Electrotypers Union, 1945-1953; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - International Transportation Association, 1953; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Internation Typographical Union, 1953-1955; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - International Union Automobiles, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America, 1946-1955; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - International Union of DOll and Toy Workers, 1953; Series 1 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors, November 1951; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - International Union of Electrical Radio and Machine Workers, CIO, 1953; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - International Union of Life Insurance Agents, 1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - International Union of Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1946-1950; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - International Union of operating Engineers, 1928-1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - International Union of United Automobile Workers, 1949-1953; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - International Union of United Brewery Workers, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, and Soft Drink Workers of America, September 1929; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - International Union United Mine Workers of America, 1956; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - International Union of United Steelworkers of America, 1964-1978; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - International Wood Carvers Association, 1930; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - International Woodworkers of America, 1945-1952; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - joint Council of Dining Car Employees, 1939-1941; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Journeyman, Barbers, Hairdressers, 1949; Series 1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Journeymen Stone Cutters Association of North America, 1946; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Laborers' International Union of North America, September 1996; series 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Local Union, No. 623, 1919; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Local 682, 1951-1963; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Local Union 688, 1969; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Local 787, November 27, 1940; Series 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Maryland Division Sick Fund, May 1945; Series 1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Missouri Pacific Railroad Co., 1937; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Mechanical Department Association New Haven RR, 1928; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Mechanical Department Association of the Burlington Railroad, 1931; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Metal Publishers, Suffers, Platers and Helpers, 1943-1947; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Forces Assoication Pennsylvania Railroad Association, 1924-1928; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Missouri-Kansas-Texas Association Of Shop Employees, 1928; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Maintenance of Way Employes Union, 1934; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Maintenance of Way Foremen's Association Union Pacific System, 1929; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - National Federation of post Office Clerks, 1946-1952; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - National Association of Postal Supervisors, 1946-1954; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - National Association of Post Office Custodial Emp., 1946; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - National League of District Postmasters of the US, 1946-1951; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - National Council Railway Patrolmen's Union, 1942; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - National Independent Union Council, 1953; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - National Association Of International Revenue Employees, 1952-1954; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - National Association of Letter Carriers, 1946-1954; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1947; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - National Association of Post Office Mechanics, 1945; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - National Association of Special Delivery Messengers, 1947; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - National Postal Transport Association, 1949-1956; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - National Agricultural Workers Union A.F. of L., 1952; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - National Association of Broadcast Employees and Tecnicians, 1953; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - National Customs Service Association, 1953; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - National Alliance of Postal Employees, 1941; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - National Federation of Salaried Workers, 1949; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - National Metal Trades Association, 1918; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - National Conference of State Legislative Representitives Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1949; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - National Association of Special Delivery Messengers, 1952; Series 1 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - National Federation of Federal Employees, 1946-1960; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - National Marine Engineers Beneficial Association, 1935-1964; Series 1 (Box 12, Folder 2)